[Music]
being it to the game yeah I don't want
to leave it and maybe we're going to the
game
well we go now to see someone about my
job you understand what oh you're gonna
gain I said possibly we're going to the
game
you know what possibly means like
probably no probably means there's a
good chance that we're going possibly
means we might we might not well just
probably meaning we have a good chance
what does possibly mean I know what it
means what does it mean it means that
we're not going to the game how did you
get so smart
over there yeah
[Music]
was the ribbon yeah
how are you sir Chris Gardner Dean
Witter oh hi hi this is my son
Christopher hey hey hey Christopher what
are you doing up here
I came to apologize for missing our
appointment the other day Colleen you
need to come up
oh no Activ we were in the neighborhood
visiting a very close friend of ours and
I just wanted to take this opportunity
to say thank you for your time I know
you've probably waited for me a little
bit I want you to know that I do not
take that for granted no come on what's
in this the an osteoma National
bone-density scanner
oh yeah company I bought it two prior to
go into work at Witter I have a meeting
after the game you guys know into the
game oh yeah possibly possibly yeah
we're going to I'm taking my son Tim my
12 year old we were just leaving here
listen we'll get out of your way again
thank you very much and I'm sorry about
the other day and I hope that we can
reschedule for later this week you got
it
thank you very much sir you take care
here come on say bye bye Chris
bye Christopher hey you guys want to
come with us
well uh to Candlestick we're going now
come with us we're your seats we've
we're upper deck we got a box come on
you want to sit the box no well it's not
actually a but it's a private section
it's more comfortable you want to go
okay
okay kids in the back hey once you put
that your car yeah oh sure sure oh my
god what happened I think I got stung by
a bee
you all right oh yeah you're not
allergic no no yeah back of my head are
you okay yeah I'm fine Christopher
for fun
Christopher sit back sit back